Guide to the Cecile Pineda Papers, 1959 - 1998
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6. Audiovisual materials
  - Subseries 2. Theatre of Man performance tapes
    - Threesomes at All Saints' Waller Street, San Francisco, 1977, Creator's Id No. 15.05; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3. Theatre of Man rehearsal tapes
    - Serpent rehearsal, "Creation", "Begats", 1971, Creator's Id No. 15.06; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Serpent rehearsal, "Cain & Abel", 1971, Creator's Id No. 15.07; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Serpent rehearsal, Fort Cronkite, 1971, Creator's Id No. 15.08; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Stoneground rehearsal,1974, Creator's Id No. 15.1; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Stoneground rehearsal,1974, Creator's Id No. 15.11; 1 videoreel of 1: sd., col.; 1/2 in. Memorex chroma (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Eurydice rehearsal, "Search", "Mirrors", 1972, Creator's Id No. 15.9; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 4. Theatre of Man miscellany
    - Rehearsal: sound environments, Creator's Id No. 15.12; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Rehearsal: sound environments, Creator's Id No. 15.13; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Rehearsal: sound environments, Creator's Id No. 15.14; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Eleanor Sully KPFA interviews Cecile Leneman nee Pineda, 1971, Creator's Id No. 15.15; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Eleanor Sully KPFA interviews Cecile Leneman nee Pineda, 1971, Creator's Id No. 15.16; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dup (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - R.G. tape, Creator's Id No. 15.17; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Theater of Man: Fool of the world, Creator's Id No. 15.19; 1 videoreel of 1: sd., col.; 1/2 in. Sony video tape, no. V-30H, for Helical Scan Video recorders (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Medea, Creator's Id No. 15.2; slides; 35 mm. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Dolores, Creator's Id No. 15.18; 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 1)
  - Subseries 5. Author appearances
    - Larry Johnson KOME inteview1985, Creator's Id No. 8.01; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Russ Olner KPEN / Jeff Charles KSTP interviews1985, Creator's Id No. 8.02; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Raimundo Franco interview KUSF1986, Creator's Id No. 8.03; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - A. Carroll & D. Volpendesta interview1986, Creator's Id No. 8.04; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - National Writers Union fiction panel, 1987, and Prof. Deepak Mehta, S.N.D.T. Univ., Bombay, 1988, Creator's Id No. 8.05; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Jose Amaya interview1988, Creator's Id No. 8.06; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Cecile Pineda: regents lecture, USB, 1988, Creator's Id No. 8.07; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Marty Maas-Cohane WHYY interview1989, Creator's Id No. 8.08; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Kathleen Stevenson KBOO interview1998, Creator's Id No. 8.09; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Denny Smithson KPFA interview1992, Creator's Id No. 8.1; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Padraigin McGillicuddy KPFA interview1992, Creator's Id No. 8.11; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Prof. Michele Driscoll, University of Maui interview,1986, Creator's Id No. 8.12; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Peter Carroll Book talk, KPFA interview1986, Creator's Id No. 8.13; 1 sound cassette: analog (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Face read by the author, Part I / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.14; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Face read by the author, Part I / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.15; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Face read by the author, Part II / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.16; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Face read by the author, Part II / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.17; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Pineda lecture, Univ. of California, Santa Barbara, 1996 May 24, Creator's Id No. 8.3; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Audiocorrections FACE readings for KPFA1985, Creator's Id No. 8.32 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Face read by the author, Part III / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.18; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Face read by the author, Part IV / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.19; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Face read by the author, Part V / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.2; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Face read by the author, Part VI / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.21; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 1 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.22; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 2 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.23; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 3 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.24; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 4 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.25; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 5 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.26; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 6 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.27; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 7 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.28; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Frieze read by the author, Reel 8 / produced by KPFA, Berkeley, Calif., Creator's Id No. 8.29; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. dupe (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Learning to cope, in which Pineda talks about tension management, 1978 Summer, Creator's Id No. 8.31; 1 reel of 1: sd., col.; 16 mm. (Box 2)
- Series 7. Posters
  - After Eurydice: Musical Score (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - After Eurydice: Posters, Poster Layout (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Curtain Up: Poster (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Murder in the Cathedral: Musical Score (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Stoneground: Posters and Publicity Photographs, Previews (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - The Serpent: Oversized Photographs (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - The Serpent: Posters (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - The Trial: Posters (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Theatre of Man: Audtion and Workshop Posters (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Theatre of Man: Unknown Show Poster Layout (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Time/Piece, Poster (Box 57, Folder 9)